Guide to the Walter E. Fauntroy papers, Part III, 1930-2006 MS2394
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Walter E. Fauntroy papers, Part III
1930-2006
1990-2006
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Charles Sumner School (Washington, D.C.)
MS2394
11.5 Linear Feet
Walter E. Fauntroy is a civil rights and religious leader in Washington, DC, with a career spanning over sixty years. Fauntroy served previously as delegate to the House of Representatives for Washington, DC; pastor of New Bethel Baptist Church; and as director of Walter E. Fauntroy and Associates (a Washington, DC-based consulting firm)--among many other things. This collection contains administrative files, project proposals, speeches, correspondence, financial and legal documents, church sermons, church administrative documents, religious sheet music, and personal papers. These materials date from 1930-2006, with the bulk of the records falling between 1990 and 2006.
Related Materials
Within Special Collections Research Center: MS2070 Walter E. Fauntroy papers, part 1 MS2310 Walter Fauntroy Papers Part II
Other related materials are located at various institutions across the United States, often within collections that document Civil Rights and legislative history. This is also true for related materials spread across other collections at the Special Collections Research Center.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of the Charles Sumner School Museum and Archives, 2020 January 10 (2020.001)
Custodial History
These materials were collected by staff from the Charles Sumner School Museum and Archives in 2019. They transferred the materials to the SCRC in early 2020.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into three series: Walter E. Fauntroy personal papers, Walter E. Fauntroy and Associates files, and New Bethel Baptist Church materials. The folders within each series are arranged alphabetically. The collection was mostly in alphabetical order on arrival--although some folders have been moved to create the series or maintain the alphabetical arrangement. Because of Walter Fauntroy's personal and professional activities, there may be some overlap between his personal materials, business files, and the materials from New Bethel Baptist Church.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains administrative files, project proposals, speeches, correspondence, financial and legal documents, church sermons, church administrative documents, religious sheet music, and personal papers. These materials date from 1930-2006, with the bulk of the records falling between 1990 and 2006.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for use. However, some folders have been restricted because they contain personal or financial information. These folders will remain closed to researchers until Walter Fauntroy's death.
Biographical Note
Walter E. Fauntroy was born in Washington, D.C. on February 6, 1933. He graduated from Dunbar High School in 1952 and received his Bachelor of Arts from Virginia Union University in 1955. He earned a bachelor of divinity from Yale University Divinity School in 1958. In 1959, he began his career in public service through his appointment as pastor of his childhood church, New Bethel Baptist Church. He served as pastor from 1959 until his retirement in 2009.
An advocate of civil rights, Fauntroy served as a leader in the civil rights movement. He became close to Rev. Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr., and served as the director of the Washington Bureau of the Southern Christian Leadership Conference (SCLC) from 1960-1971. As a director of SCLC, Fauntroy coordinated the events leading up to the August 1963 March on Washington for Jobs and Freedom and the 1965 March from Selma to Montgomery, Alabama. In 1968, he served as the national coordinator of the Poor People's Campaign. In the years after Dr. King's assassination, Fauntroy often gave speeches in his honor and memory.
Fauntroy utilized his activism experiences to promote urban redevelopment within the District of Columbia. He founded a number of redevelopment projects, including the Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO), a neighborhood planning corporation. Fauntroy's active community involvement led to his first political position as the first vice chairman appointed to the District of Columbia Council in 1967. He became a vocal advocate for voting rights and representation within the District (among other things). Later in his career, in the mid-1990s, Fauntroy was heavily involved with work surrounding the Capital Homestead Act, which would have created opportunities for Black residents to own property within the District. It was supposedly based off of the Homestead Acts of the mid-1800s. The legislation did not pass.
In 1970, Congress passed the Delegate Act, and in 1971, D.C residents elected Fauntroy to represent the District as Delegate to the House of Representatives. Fauntroy strongly supported the right for full representation of the District, and immediately began a legislative campaign in support of home rule. In 1973, the District of Columbia Self-Government and Government Reorganization Act became law and D.C. citizens were given the authority to elect a mayor and a city council. He was also an advocate for D.C. Statehood.
Fauntroy served in Congress for twenty years (1971-1991). He worked on many committees during his tenure, including the Congressional Black Caucus (CBC), for which he also served as chairman. In addition to serving on many committees, he also chaired several of them. He founded the National Black Leadership Roundtable (NBLR), a network created under the auspices of the CBC, in support of domestic leadership. The "Free South Africa Movement" (FSAM) and the Congressional Task Force on Haiti serve as two examples of Fauntroy's active involvement in international affairs (which would continue after leaving Congress).
Fauntroy founded his own consulting firm, Walter E. Fauntroy and Associates, which was based in Washington, DC. After leaving Congress, he was involved in many local, national, and international projects and causes. He lobbied Congress on international issues, specifically in South Africa and the Middle East. He also worked on issues within the Washington metro area, like the relocation of the Lorton Prison Complex, the Capital Homestead Act, and other projects in conjunction with the NBLR, and other Baptist and Interfaith groups. He was frequently asked to speak at conferences and events--usually promoting a project he was working on or commemorating Civil Rights history. He also served as an advisor and counselor to individuals who might have known him through his position at New Bethel.
Fauntroy retired as pastor of New Bethel in 2009. His wife, Dorothy, served as First Lady of the Church while Walter was pastor. They have two children, Marvin and Melissa.
(Biography adapted from the Finding Guides written for MS2070 Walter Fauntroy papers Part 1 and MS2310 Walter Fauntroy papers Part 2, with new portions added in 2021. For more information on Walter Fauntroy and his achievements, please see those Finding Guides.)
Civil rights movements; United States -- District of Columbia -- Washington; Churches -- Washington (D.C.); Urban renewal; International relations; Political consultants; Politicians; Charles Sumner School (Washington, D.C.); Fauntroy, Walter E.
- Walter E. Fauntroy personal papers, 1950-1996; circa 1950s-1960s; MS2394 Series 1
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains personal correspondence, academic records and materials, and personal writings. The materials date from the 1950s to 1996, with the bulk of the materials from circa 1950s to 1960s.
  Conditions Governing Access
  This series contains some folders have been restricted and will remain closed to researchers until Walter Fauntroy's death.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  - Academic Work, Early Sermons, and Pastoral Duties, circa 1950s-1960s; MS2394 Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Sermons, and Speeches, circa 1950s-1960s; MS2394 Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence to and from Walter Fauntroy, 1964-1965; MS2394 Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Letters of Support [Financial Disclosure Court Case] [1/2], 1994-1995, undated; MS2394 Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Letters of Support [Financial Disclosure Court Case] [2/2], 1994-1995, undated; MS2394 Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Personal Papers and Documents on Economic Development, 1959, 1965; MS2394 Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Program, "A Belated Birthday Celebration for Our Pastor," Rev. John J. Koger, New Bethany Baptist Church, 1959 February 18; MS2394 Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Book, "A Call to Conscience: The Landmark Speeches of Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr." and Letter to Walter Fauntroy from Coretta Scott King, 2001; MS2394 Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Note about Folder
    Walter Fauntroy wrote the introduction to King's speech "Give Us the Ballot." This copy appears to be sent from Coretta Scott King and the King Center. Coretta Scott King wrote an inscription to Fauntroy inside the book.
- Walter E. Fauntroy and Associates files, 1981-2006; 1994-1999; MS2394 Series 2
  This series is arranged alphabetically by folder title. In cases where a more descriptive title was added, the folder is still organized based on the original folder title. For more information about folder titles, please see the Processing Information note at the collection level.
  - 30th Anniversary of the March on Washington and other materials, 1988, 1990, 1993-1994, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 30th Anniversary of the March on Washington and other materials, 1988, 1990, 1993-1994, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - AA Gifts Requests for Payment Form, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Addresses on the Martin Luther King Jr. Holiday Celebration/Capital Homestead Act, 1996 January; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Amer. Bapt College, 1995 November 16; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - BEDC Request for Payment Form, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Bethune DuBois [Remarks to the Bethune-DuBois Association Members' Forum], 1995, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Bethune 2 [Bethune-DuBois Forum], 1996 November 21; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Black Church Communications Network - First-Ever Nationwide Black Church GOTV Video Confer., 1996; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Black Church Communications Network - Heads of Denominations, 1996, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Black Church Communications Network - July Memo, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Black Church Communications Network Stationery, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Black Church Communications Network - Sykes Communications, 1997, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Blk Church Leadership Plan [Black Church Moral Leadership Strategy], 1995, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - CACS [Church Association for Community Services], 1995-1996; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - CACS [Church Association for Community Services Materials], 1995-1996; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Capital Empowerment Hub Proposal and Schematics, 1995, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - CBC GOTV [Congressional Black Caucus Get-Out-the-Vote Drives], 1996 March 9; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - CBC Presentation [Congressional Black Caucus Annual Retreat, March 6, 1999], 1996 March 9; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Church Association for Community Services - Covenant of Faith, 1997, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Church Association for Community Services "Covenant of Faith", 1997; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Church Association for Community Services - Food Program, 1997; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Church Association for Community Services - Press Releases, 1997-1998; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Church Association for Community Services Stationery, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Congress of National Black Churches, 1996; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Convention Date Returns [NBLR Voter Registration Outreach], 2006, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - D.C. Homestead Act [Correspondence & Proposals], 1996; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Dept. of Agriculture [Address to the Department of Agriculture], 1996 January 11; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Downtown Cluster of Congregations, 1994-1995, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Effects of Marriage (The Heritage Foundation), 2002 April; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Faith-Based Intiative - Apgar Memorandum, 2000 March 31; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Faith-Based Initiative - Cuomo Memorandum - 3/31/00, 2000 March 31; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Faith-Based White House [Washington Post Article], 2001 January 30; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Faith, Inc. (Fund for Afforable Innercity Turnkey Housing), 2003 May 14; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Fallen Soliders Request For Payment Form, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Farrell, George [Department of Housing and Human Development Grants], 1997; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Fauntroy Bio/Transafrica Forum [Walter Fauntroy Curriculum Vita], 1999, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Fax Cover Sheets [National Black Leadership Roundtable Fax Cover Sheets and Correspondence], 2006, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Fisher, Henry, 2000 August 16; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Fomenko, The Hon. Alexander [Russian, African, and African American Relations], 2003-2004; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Gephart, Richard A. / Frost, Martin, 1996, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Giffert, Paul [Proposal for the Campaign to Build on Black Family Reunion], undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Gregory, Dick [Middle East Affairs], 2005, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Greider, William (Bill), 1996-1997, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Griffith, Reginald [African Affiars, Correspondence with George H.W. and George W. Bush], 2000-2001, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Habib Investments, Ltd. [Middle East Affairs], 2002, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Hamilton, Lee, 1999, 2006, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Hastings, Hon. Alcee L., undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Hendon, Rickey R., 1997; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Herman, Alexis M. [Labor Secretary Alexis M. Herman/Global Family Day], 1997, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Hill, Rene, 1997 May 12; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Historical Black Church Leadership Forum - Political Mobilization Strategy, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Historical Black Church Resurrection Crusade, 1995-1996, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Historically Black Church Business Enterprises Discussions, 1997, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - HNIC - National Black Church Satellite Network Proposal, 1996, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Homestead Act Flyer, 1995, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Howard University Divinity School, 1996; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Ill. Leg. Black Caucus [Illinois Legislative Caucus Conference], 1997 April; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Incoming Mail, 2006; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Instructions [Capital Homestead Act], 1996-1997, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Instructions [Capital Homestead Act Petition], undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Johnson, Eddie Bernice [Congressional Black Caucus], 2000, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Johnson, Peter [Capital Homestead Act], 1995-1997, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Joint Center for Political And Economic Studies - Faith Based Initiatives and Black Churches, 2001-2002, 2005; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Kagimu, Habib [Congress/Middle East Affairs], 2002-2004, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Kennedy, Edward M., 2005 November 1; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - King Holiday Commission, 1996; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - King Holiday Extension Act, 1989, 1993; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - King Holiday Program [Martin Luther King Jr. Commemoration Programs], 1999, 2000; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - King Holiday Speech - 1995 - Riyadh, Saudi Arabia, 1994, 1995; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - King Holiday Speech - 1997 - B On Occasion of the Celebration, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - King Holiday Speech - 1997 - D Environ. Protection Agency, 1997 January 14; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - King Holiday Speech - 1997 - E Dept. of Health & Human Services, 1995, 1997; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - King Holiday Speech - 1997 - F Department of the Navy, 1997 January 16; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Lane, Ambrose (Show) [Guest Hosting Script], 1995 June 6, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Le Pen [Jany Le Pen / Middle East Affairs], 1996, 2000, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Letter from Walter Fauntroy regarding the Republican Financing of Arthur Davis' Campaign, 2002 April 25; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Mandela, Nelson [Address to the Joint Houses of Congress], 1994 October 6; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Marriage Alliance [Position on Same-sex Marriage and the Federal Marriage Amendment] [1/2], 2001-2005; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Marriage Alliance [Position on Same-sex Marriage and the Federal Marriage Amendment] [2/2], 2001-2005; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Memorandum to Wyvetter H. Younge on Capital Homesteading in Illinois, 1997 April; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Metropolitan Baptist Church [Neighborhood Empowerment Team], 1996-1997; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Missionary Baptist Ministers Membership Directory - 2003, 2003, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - MLK Day, 1996 January 15; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Middleburg College, 1996 January 14; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Misc. Statements [given by Walter Fauntory], 1990, 1994-1995, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Namibia Catholic Bishop's Conference [African Affairs], 1981, 2002-2003, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - National African American Clergy Committee (NAACC) ["Gideon's Solider"], 1992 November 3; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - National African American Clergy Committee (5/13/96 Report), 1996; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - National Baptist Convention, USA, INC. [Correspondence and Reports], 1994, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - National Baptist Convention, USA, INC. - Revelation Corp. of America, 1996; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - National Black Church Communications Network (6/10/96 Report), 1996 June; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - National Black Church Satellite Network Proposal, 1996; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - National Missionary Baptist Convention of American [Homestead Act and Super Empowerment Zone], 1996; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - National Office of Black Catholics [Captial Homestead Act, Super Empowerment Zone and Gideon Army], 1996; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - NBLR Flyers - 2006, 2006, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - NBLR - GOTV Request for Payment Form [National Black Leadership Roundtable - Get-Out-the-Vote Request for Payment Form], undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - NBLR - Speaking Engagements at National Conventions - 2006 GOTV, MS2394 Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - NBTC Board [New Birth Corporation Inc. and the Capital Homestead Initiative Team], 1995; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - NBTC Correspondence [New Birth Transformation Corporation, Lorton Prison Replacement, DC Empowerment Zone], 1995, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - NBTC Packet [New Birth Transformation Corporation Proposal], undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - New Birth Transformation Corporation, Democratic National Committee, 1996, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - New NBLR Letterhead [Letter to Dr. Joe Leonard], 2006 August 15, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - New Articles [on Economics], 1995, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Nov. 15 CACS Speech, 1995 November; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Nov. 16 Attendence [Capital Homestead Act], undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Organization Chart [Proposed Board of Directors of the New Birth Corporation, Inc.], 1995 December 11; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Panelists for Sept 9th Forum [NBLR "When Black Folks Vote" Forum], 2006; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Petitions [Blank Capital Homestead Act Petitions], undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Pie Charts [Distribution of Corporate Ownership], undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Presentation [Presentation Statement on New Birth Transformation Center], undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Press [Personal and Professional], 1986-1987, 1995, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Progressive National Baptist Convention - Capital Homestead Act [Press Releases and Fax Sheets], 1996; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Progressive National Baptist Convention Speech, 1997 January 23; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Progressive National Baptist Convention - Super Economic Empowerment Plan, 1996, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Progressive National Baptist Convention, Inc. 41st Annual Sess., 2002; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Progressive National Baptist Convention, Inc. - 43rd Annual Sess., 2004 August; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Progressive National Baptist Convention, Inc. - Articles of Incorporation, 1994, udated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Religious Coalition for Reproductive Choice, 1996-1997; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Remarks to the Bethune-DuBois Association Members' Forum, 1995 November 29; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Responsible Father [Charles Ballard], 1982, 1995, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Return Address Labels - African American Gifts, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Return Address Labels - Business Enterprise Development Company, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Return Address Labels - Fallen Soliders, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Rev. Fauntroy Travel Schedules, 2006; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Saudi Arabia Trip Information, 1995, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Speaking Engagements (Pending), 2006, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Speech - General File, 1995-1997, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Spirit Fest, 1997 April; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Soros Version [Statement on Capital Homestead Act], undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - South Africa Federal Reserve Bank [Research and Correspondence on Banking and South Africa] [1/2], 1993-1995, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - South Africa Federal Reserve Bank [Research and Correspondence on Banking and South Africa] [2/2], 1993-1995, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Telecommunications, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Telemedicine, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Telephone Messages, 2006, undated; MS2394 Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 15)